let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is not an open source software?",
    answer: "Microsoft Office",
    options: [
      "MySQL",
      "GNU image manipulation",
      "Microsoft Office",
      "Libre Office"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "An example of web design OSS",
    answer: "Nvu",
    options: [
      "Open Office",
      "Nvu",
      "AbiWorld",
      "KOffice"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What do you understand from GNOME and KDE?",
    answer: "GUI Based Linux",
    options: [
      "Linux Distribution",
      "Command Lines",
      "GUI Based Linux",
      " File Framework"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who was the founder of Linux?",
    answer: "Linus Torvalds",
    options: [
      "Bill Gates",
      "Christopher Markin",
      "IBM",
      "Linus Torvalds"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the least amount of memory you would require to run a Linux?",
    answer: "4 Megabyte (Mb)",
    options: [
      "4 Megabyte (Mb)",
      "2 Megabyte (Mb)",
      "64 Megabyte (Mb)",
      "16 Megabyte (Mb)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is a way to associate styles with your HTML document?",
    answer: "Both of the above",
    options: [
      " External CSS - The Element",
      "Imported CSS - @import Rule",
      "Both of the above",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following property is used to set the background color of an element?",
    answer: "background-color",
    options: [
      "background-color",
      "background-image",
      "background-repeat",
      "background-position"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following property specifies the distance between a marker and the text in the list?",
    answer: "marker-offset",
    options: [
      "list-style-position",
      "marker-offset",
      "list-style-image",
      "list-style"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following property is used to set the width of an image?",
    answer: "width",
    options: [
      "border",
      "width",
      "-moz-opacity",
      "height"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following property changes the style of right border?",
    answer: ":border-right-style",
    options: [
      ":border-bottom-style",
      ":border-left-style",
      ":border-top-style",
      ":border-right-style"
    ]
  },
  
];